A Guide to the Peter Mellette Papers, 1945-1993
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Peter Mellette Papers, 1945-1993
The Library of Virginia
39459
37.2 cubic feet (78 boxes)
Mellette, Peter, 1920-1993
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
The collection is made up of two accessions. The original accession (comprising almost the entire collection) was purchased from Crown Collectibles, Richmond, Virginia, on 10 April 2001 (Accession 39459). A handful of additional materials was donated to the Library on 3 December 2002 by Sommer Wickham, Richmond (Accession 40332). The two accessions have been combined and are filed here jointly as Accession 39459.
Biographical Information
Peter Augustus Mellette was born in Latta, South Carolina, on 10 January 1920, to parents Frank Mellette (1892-1944) and Floy Bethea Mellette (d. 1953). Although born in Latta, where his mother had family connections, Mellette spent his earliest years in Watkins Glen, New York. The family relocated to Latta in 1923, the first of several moves to various South Carolina towns (also including Lone Star, Boykin, and Sharon). He completed his undergraduate education at Furman University in 1940, then moved to Pennsylvania to attend Crozer Theological Seminary. It was during his time in Pennsylvania that Mellette met (Mary) Sue Jackson (1922-2000), whom he married on 16 June 1943.
After Mellette's graduation from Crozer in 1944, the couple moved to Columbus, Ohio. Sue Mellette worked on her medical degree at the University of Cincinnati while Peter served as pastor of a federated Baptist-Presbyterian church in Johnstown. Beginning in 1947, he pastored the United Church in Garrettsville, Ohio, while pursuing a master's degree in history at Case Western Reserve University. Upon completion of the degree in 1949, the Mellettes moved to New York City, where Peter earned a doctorate in education at Columbia University in 1951.
After a brief stint as pastor of Speed Memorial Church in Speed, Indiana, Peter Mellette accepted a position as assistant director for the St. Louis (Mo.) area of the National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ) in 1952. The next year, he moved to Richmond to become the director of the organization's Virginia region. Here he spent the remainder of his career, taking on additional roles as field director for the Carolinas, Kentucky, and Tennessee in 1973 (later adding Ohio and Indiana); national vice president in 1975; and senior vice president in 1978. He entered partial retirement in 1981, stepping down from his Virginia directorship but continuing with his national-level responsibilities until retiring fully in 1982.
The NCCJ formed in 1928, when reactions to the presidential candidacy of Al Smith revealed a powerful strain of anti-Catholic sentiment in America. Aiming to combat such religious bigotry, the organization's founding focus was the promotion of interreligious cooperation and understanding, particularly among Protestants, Catholics, and Jews. Over the years, as the struggle against racial bias took precedence on the national stage, the NCCJ had to decide whether to advocate for interracial as well as interreligious harmony.
Mellette, heading up a Southern branch of the organization in the tumultuous decades of the Civil Rights Movement, fielded criticism from people on both sides of the issue. His papers highlight this variety of opinions and pressures, containing for example letters from individuals denouncing NCCJ for recommending even obliquely pro-integration literature, and others decrying the lack of diversity in the faces pictured in NCCJ publications. He was also frequently called upon to defend the organization's emphasis on education rather than activism.
At the end of his career, Mellette was praised for having a calming yet progressive influence during a difficult era. The various programs with which he was most closely associated--including Youth Seminars on Intergroup Relations, Dialogue groups, and Police-Community Relations workshops--were designed to bring people of various groups together to discuss human relations problems in an open and civil manner.
Mellette died of a heart attack on 3 February 1993. He was survived by his wife, Susan (a professor of medical oncology and director of the Cancer Rehabilitation Program at the Medical College of Virginia), their daughter, Susan Mellette Lederhouse, and son, Peter Mason Mellette.
Some of the above biographical information was taken from Peter Mellette's memoirs, Some of Life's Moments, which can be found at the Virginia Historical Society, Richmond, Va. (Call number CT275 .M48)
Scope and Content
Papers, 1945-1993, of Dr. Peter Mellette (1920-1993), longtime director of the Virginia region of the National Conference of Christians and Jews (NCCJ). Almost all of the papers in the collection relate to Mellette's work with the NCCJ, and include correspondence; general NCCJ files, such as administrative reports, committee and local chapter files, manuals, news releases, and newsletters; outreach and program files, including brochures, discussion guides, manuals, resource packets, scripts for radio and television spots and plays, sound recordings, syllabi, and other materials from programs such as Brotherhood Week, Rearing Children of Good Will, and Police-Community Relations, as well as various awards programs; subject files reflecting Mellette's interests in education, race relations, religion, school desegregation, social justice, and other topics; financial papers including budget projections, financial statements, and fundraising files; and an extensive collection of clippings.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. NCCJ general files
Series III. NCCJ outreach and program files
Series IV. Subject files
Series V. NCCJ financial papers
Series VI. Clippings and magazines
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence, 1945-1993., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 1-8)
  Some of the early correspondence in this series was created by Clarence Wagner and Joseph Murphy, Peter Mellette's two predecessors in the position of director of NCCJ's Virginia region. Reflecting the progress and the struggles of the fledgling division, these letters reveal efforts to build the reputation of the organization in the area, raise funds, develop new programs, establish relationships between local representatives of the various religions, and explain and defend the NCCJ's mission and methods. There are also a handful of letters from Mellette's brief tenure as associate director of the St. Louis (Mo.) region.
  When he took the helm of the Virginia region in 1953, Mellette faced many of the same challenges that Wagner and Murphy had encountered. These included concern among religious leaders that the NCCJ aimed for assimilation rather than simple cooperation, impatience with its focus on education instead of activism, and differing viewpoints on how the organization should respond to the Civil Rights Movement. Of note here is a September 1956 letter from Virginius Dabney, editor of the Richmond Times-Dispatch. In it, Dabney offered his opinion that the NCCJ would have trouble garnering support in the South if they drifted from a focus on interfaith relations to a more general emphasis on the brotherhood of man.
  On the whole, correspondence is fairly routine and administrative in nature, showing both the planning of and follow-up to various NCCJ programs, Mellette's work cultivating contacts in the religious, business, government, and education communities, NCCJ staff news, travel arrangements, fundraising, and updates on the organization's finances. A substantial collection of memos from the national office can be found among these materials. Also included are letters, 1947-1989, from a binder kept by Mellette. Several of the items here come from notable figures including Dwight Eisenhower, Brooks Hays, J. Lindsay Almond, and Harry F. Byrd, Jr., and reference either involvement with or requests to participate in NCCJ programs.
  General correspondence is arranged chronologically. In some cases, Mellette kept separate folders for correspondence with specific individuals; these have been maintained and are filed after the general correspondence. Please note that additional letters from these individuals may appear in the general correspondence files.
  - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, 1956, cont'd. (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1968, cont'd. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2-4)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Andrew Gottschall, 1961-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1956, cont'd. (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence, Bill Tipton, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Clarence Wagner, 1945-1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Everett Clinchy, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence, Gordon Lovejoy, 1953-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
  - Correspondence, Herbert Seamans, 1952-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Sterling Brown, 1950-1972 (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous notable correspondence (deconstructed binder), 1947-1989 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
- Series II. NCCJ general files, 1945-1986., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 8-17)
  Series consists of files pertaining to the administration, organization, and promotion of the National Conference of Christians and Jews, with an emphasis on Peter Mellette's Virginia region. Materials include brochures and other informational literature, newsletters, news releases, files on local chapters, papers relating to various committees and boards, and training manuals. See Series III for files on the programs offered by the NCCJ, and Series IV for information on the organization's fundraising activities and finances.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Brotherhood magazine, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Building Brotherhood in Your Community pilot project (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - By-laws (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Catholic list (special), Richmond (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Community Organizations, 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Community Organizations, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Community Organizations, 1955-1960, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1950, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1953, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Educational Organizations, 1959, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Mass Communications, 1952-1955 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Religious Organizations, 1947-1953 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Commission on Religious Organizations, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Religious Organizations, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Conference magazine, 1945-1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - The Dialogue bulletin, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - The Dialogue bulletin, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Field and Program Service Bulletin, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Field and Program Service Bulletin, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Future Action Planning Committee, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - A Futures Study for the National Conference of Christians and Jews, Part II, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Harrisonburg chapter (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Martinsville chapter (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - Membership drives, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Membership lists and directories (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous administrative papers (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous staff biographies (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - National Staff Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - National Staff Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Staff Committee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - National Staff Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - National Staff Conference, 8-12 January 1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    See also an oversize group photograph (rolled) taken at the National Staff Conference, 9 January 1967. To see this photograph, request Box 78.
  - National Staff Conference, 6-9 January 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Staff Conference, 6-9 January 1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - National Staff Conference, 26-29 March 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NCCJ 20th anniversary, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - NCCJ 50th anniversary, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - NCCJ Advisory Board (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - NCCJ annual meetings, board meetings, etc., 1945-1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NCCJ annual meetings, board meetings, etc., 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - NCCJ annual meetings, board meetings, etc., 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NCCJ annual meetings, board meetings, etc., 1968-1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NCCJ annual meetings, board meetings, etc., 1982, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NCCJ brochures and general information (Box 12, Folder 5-9)
  - NCCJ brochures and general information, cont'd. (Box 13, Folder 1-8)
  - NCCJ name change debate, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - NCCJ news releases, 1946-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - NCCJ news releases, 1968-1982 and undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1950-1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1954-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - NCCJ newsletters, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk chapter (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
  - Norfolk chapter, cont'd. (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - The Organization and Development of New Chapters, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Peninsula chapter (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - President's Council, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Protestant list (special), Richmond (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Report: How Can We Improve NCCJ's Public Relations? 10 November 1959 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Report: The National Conference: Self-Evaluation, ca. 1957 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Resources for speakers and discussion leaders (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - Resources for speakers and discussion leaders, cont'd. (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Richmond chapter (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Roanoke chapter (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Southern Staff Conference, 4-5 March 1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Staff Relations/Representative Advisory Council, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Staff Relations/Representative Advisory Council, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Staff Relations/Representative Advisory Council, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Staff Relations/Representative Advisory Council / National Staff Committee, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Staff Relations/Representative Advisory Council / National Staff Committee, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Staff training (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Suffolk chapter (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - Virginia Beach chapter (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Virginia region (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Your Job with NCCJ, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Series III. NCCJ outreach and program file, 1946-1988., Extent: 27 boxes. (Box 18-44)
  Outreach and program files, 1946-1988, reflect the NCCJ's focus on educational efforts rather than direct activism. In general, materials include program syllabi and agendas, planning materials, annual and program reports of the national office and various regional offices, and manuals articulating policies and describing past programs. Several of the programs with which Mellette was more directly involved are represented in greater volume than others. These include Rearing Children of Good Will, Police-Community Relations, various youth programs, and NCCJ's signature program, Brotherhood Week.
  Perhaps the most visible and far-reaching of the NCCJ's efforts, Brotherhood Week was designed to promote the organization's guiding ideal of the "brotherhood of mankind under the fatherhood of God." Typically falling during the week of George Washington's birthday, the program consisted of media promotions in radio, television, newspapers, and movie theater newsreels; lectures, the showing of films, panel discussions, and other programs at schools and colleges, places of worship, and community organization meetings; billboards; high-profile chairpersons; mayoral, gubernatorial, and presidential proclamations; awards banquets; concerts; and other events. Observances were organized at both the local and national level.
  Brotherhood Week materials gathered here include agendas; brochures and other promotional literature; committee reports; correspondence; guides for speakers; invitations and programs; invoices; photographs; posters; press kits with suggested editorials, public service announcement scripts, etc.; press releases; resource lists; speech transcripts; and other items. Included are copies of Brotherhood Week addresses, statements, and proclamations made by William Tuck, Harry Truman, Douglas MacArthur, John S. Battle, Dwight Eisenhower, Thomas B. Stanley, John F. Kennedy, J. Lindsay Almond, Albertis Harrison, Lyndon Johnson, Mills Godwin, Linwood Holton, and Brooks Hays, among others. Also included is an audio recording of several brief radio spots for the 1965 observance of Brotherhood Week, one of which features the voice of Mitch Miller.
  Also included in this series are papers relating to various awards bestowed by the NCCJ. The accompanying dinner events served as one of the main sources of funds to keep the organization in operation. Peter Mellette is credited with founding the National Brotherhood Citation Dinner in Richmond in 1963, and later bringing it to other cities around the state.
  Researchers should also consult Series I, as much of the correspondence filed there deals with NCCJ programs.
  - Anytown workshops (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Awards, 1953-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood Awards manual, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Brotherhood Awards, 1960, 1965-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood Awards, 1970-1976, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinner, 11 December 1963 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood Citation Dinners, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood Dinners/Banquets, 1946-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood Dinners/Banquets, 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1946 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood Week, 22-29 February 1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1949 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1950 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Brotherhood Week, 18-25 February 1951 (Box 21, Folder 5-7)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1952 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1952, cont'd. (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Brotherhood Week, 15-22 February 1953 (Box 22, Folder 3-6)
  - Brotherhood Week, 21-28 February 1954 (Box 22, Folder 7-9)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1956 (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1957 (Box 23, Folder 6-8)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9-10)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1958, cont'd. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Week, 15-22 February 1958 (Box 24, Folder 2-4)
  - Brotherhood Week, 21-28 February 1960 (Box 24, Folder 5-8)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1961 (Box 24, Folder 9-11)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1961, cont'd. (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Brotherhood Week, 18-25 February 1962 (Box 25, Folder 3-8)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1963 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1963, cont'd. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1964 (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
  - Brotherhood Week, 21-28 February 1965 (Box 26, Folder 5-8)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1966 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1966, cont'd. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1967 (Box 27, Folder 2-4)
  - Brotherhood Week, 18-25 February 1968 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood Week, 22 February - 1 March 1970 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
  - Brotherhood Week, 14-28 February 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Brotherhood Week, 18-25 February 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood Week, 17-24 February 1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Brotherhood Week, 16-23 February 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood Week, 15-22 February 1976 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood Week, 20-27 February 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood Week, 19-26 February 1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood Week, 18-24 February 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)